







Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Jump to Section

Marital Status: Married

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Business Analyst with strong analytic and technical skills, good communication 9 years of total experience and 2.5 years of working in US.

Key Skills: business analyst, it project mgmt, project documentation, requirement gathering, business analysis, robotic process automation, solution design, Expense Management, Agile Project Management, Finance and Accounting, CSM

Green Belt Certified and Certified Scrum Master (CSM).

Work/Project Experience/Strengths:

Very effective in Customer Engagement, able to translate requirements into system requirements.

Have led requirement gathering sessions with multiple stakeholders.

Expense Management System for US based Consulting company.

Robotic Process Automation based solution design.

Strong technical skills in Software Development, experience in Microsoft technology, involved in documentation and requirement gathering from client.

About 2.5 years of US onsite experience, including working on US federal Government projects.

Can relate to the bigger picture while analyzing an application for a business needs.

Good Communication skills, able to collaborate with global teams.

Quick learner, Team player, Adaptable to change.

Work Experience

Genpact India as IT Business Analyst - Genpact Digital May 2017 to Till Date

Worked on Analysis and Design of Expense Management System for US Consulting company, application management leading UAT, application deployment, coordination with global teams of client across locations - NA EU, Asia. Requirement analysis, documentation, solution closure with client. Knowledge of RPA Tools Automation Anywhere and Open span.

Exuber Software Solutions as Project Coordinator Jun 2016 to May 2017

Coordinated and Managed Mobile app project's for multiple clients on Mobile applications.

US Dept. of Health- Center for Disease Control -Ginn Group -Northrop Grumman as IT System Analyst

Oct 2005 to Aug 2008

US Dept. of Health- Center for Disease Control (Ginn Group /Northrop Grumman)

Job Location: Atlanta, USA Oct 2007 ? Aug 2008 & Oct 2005 ? Apr 2006 Leading requirement, design and development of web applications on Microsoft Platform (ASP.NET, C#, VB.NET, SQL Server) for various Divisions of CDC (Center for Disease Control and Prevention)

Requirement analysis with clients, coordinating and development of multiple Internet facing application for NCCDPHP (National Center for Chronic Diseases).

ECS Inc (Enterprise Computing Software) as Consultant

Feb 2005 to Sep 2005

Job Location: Atlanta, USA

Worked as a Consultant on Mcrosoft Platform (ASP.NET, C#, VB.NET, SQL Server) for Georgia Dept. of Early Care and Learning (DECAL-Bright from the Start). Involved in development of PANDA(PreK Application and Database Access), Georgia's PreK program's Online Provider Service System.

Information Technologies India Ltd (ITIL) as Software Engineer Jul 2003 to Jun 2004

Team member involved in Requirement Gathering, Screen design, Prepare and Execute Test Cases, Coding, Integration and System Testing, Configuration Controller.

Bhilwara Infotech Ltd as Associate Software Engineer

Dec 2000 to Jun 2003

Worked as Associate Software Engineer, on Microsoft Platform (ASP.NET, C#, SQL Server, .net applications)

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from bca in 1999

PG: MCA (Computers) from MCA in 2006

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Green Belt certified Certified Scrum Master

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version L	ast Used	Experience
html, Xml,			
MS Project, Visio, VSS, MS Visio			
Automation Anywhere, Open Span			
SQL Server, Oracle, ERWIn			
MS Word, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.